<NAME>ResidualVM 0.2.0 - "Deliverance" released</NAME>
		<DATE>December 31st, 2014</DATE>
		<AUTHOR>bgK</AUTHOR>
		<BODY>
				<p>
					We are proud to announce the release of a new version of ResidualVM, bringing
					Myst III: Exile support, more than thirteen years after its original release.
				</p>
				<p>
					Initial work towards adding Myst III support began back in 2009 as a side project.
					A work in progress version of the engine was included in ResidualVM
					two years later. The game became completable in 2012, but only now do we feel confident
					enough to release a stable version providing a feature complete experience.
				</p>
				<p>
					Additionally, some bugs have been fixed in Grim Fandango, and game data verification.
					has been added on first launch, so that you'll know if your game data was.
					copied correctly from your CDs.
				</p>
				<p>
					Whether you are using Windows, Linux or OS X, you can go right now to our
					<a href="http://residualvm.org/downloads/">downloads page</a>, get yourself a copy of
					ResidualVM 0.2.0, and decide later if you'd rather visit the land of the dead or
					the land of a revengeful trapped man. The changes in version 0.2.0 are detailed in our
					<a href="https://github.com/residualvm/residualvm/blob/branch-0-2/NEWS">NEWS file</a>.
					Instructions to setup the games can be found on our <a href="http://wiki.residualvm.org/">wiki</a>.
				</p>
				<p>
					As usual, even though we have tested the games thoroughly you might encounter game-breaking
					bugs. So, please save often and report bugs to our
					<a href="https://github.com/residualvm/residualvm/issues">bug tracker</a>.
				</p>
				<p>
					Our thanks go to Presto Studios, for releasing such a great game, and to the people involved
					with testing ResidualVM over the years, allowing us to provide high quality releases.
				</p>
				<p>
					2015 already looks like a promising year for ResidualVM, thanks to the ongoing effort
					for adding Escape from Monkey Island support.
				</p>
		</BODY>
